A girl changes... Becoming bright,
kind, and cheerful.
A girl changes... Becoming dark,
fierce, and cruel.
"Episode Eleven:
'Angel of the Starry Night'"
I-I... Did it happen again?
D-Did what?
Sorry. To be honest, my mind's been
going blank from time to time lately.
Your mind's been going blank?
Oh, it's nothing to worry about.
I'm probably just anemic or something.
Anyway, I'm guessing you read
the note I left on your desk?
Y-Yeah. You're free Saturday?
Th-That's all I wanted to say!
Kurumi, I take it your true self's okay?
You see right through me.
The thing is, this makes it difficult
to discover why Origami turned Inverse.
Yeah, but this Origami came to
accept the death of her parents.
In which case, why did she...?
Let's go over this once more.
This world is a result of you using
Kurumi's time travel powers...
...to save Origami's parents,
who should've died five years ago...
...in order to rewrite
the history that follows.
Yeah, that's the gist of it.
I see...
Now I know why you've been
acting strange since yesterday.
However, Origami Tobiichi,
who shouldn't have inversed...
...has done so in this world
and exists now as Devil.
I've analyzed her encounter with Shin
on the roof and it shows he's not lying.
Origami Tobiichi hasn't the
faintest idea she's a Spirit.
But how can that...?
Shin, you managed to change the world.
But only you and Kurumi have knowledge
of the original world, correct?
Yeah.
As for Kurumi, her own powers
brought this about, so she's an exception.
And, guessing from your situation,
to retain knowledge of the original world,
two conditions must be met.
Being hit by Kurumi's Yod Bet, and...
...having Spirit powers
flowing through oneself.
With both those combined, memory of
the original world may be recovered.
Possibly. Origami was shot by Kurumi's
Yod Bet and went back in time.
Thanks to Shido's world change,
she's lived a peaceful life.
But when Phantom showed up
and gave her Spirit powers...
That's when she remembered it all.
Though, as a self-defense mechanism,
her memories were split in two.
Essentially, there's Origami
who lives in peace,
and the Spirit-Hunting Spirit, Devil.
As soon as Origami senses Spirit power,
she loses control of her mind and memory...
...and she's awakened as an Inverse type...
The theory works and it's consistent.
If it's true, what can we do?
As long as Origami's a Spirit,
there's only one thing for Ratatoskr to do.
Make her fall for me.
That's right. And seal her Spirit powers.
You'll need to convince
Origami to go out on a date.
--And then we can begin our--
--Uh...
What, got a problem?
Well, the truth is...
Huh?! You already promised
to meet this Saturday?!
You're telling me you hit on her
before even knowing she's a Spirit?!
Um, well, you see...
Writing a note and stuff... Since when
did I become such a girly girl?
You don't think... Is this...?
It's from Itsuka!
"Itsuka"
"Shido Itsuka"
"Sorry to invite you out of nowhere and thanks for your answer. How does Saturday at 11 in front of the station's water fountain sound?"
Gotta reply!
That date and time is all right with m--
Is that too impersonal?
"Dear Itsuka, the winds of autumn
carry in this sentimental season.
"Dear Itsuka,
the winds of autumn carry
in this sentimental season. As the moon shines like a great egg in the sky, how are you faring this"
As the moon shines like a great egg
in the sky, how are you faring this--"
What kind of girl says that?!
I appreciate you inviting
me out today, Itsuka.
Itsuka?
Uh, my pleasure.
Since we're classmates and all,
can we cut the formalities please?
U-Understood. I mean...
All right.
Good. That's more like the
Origami I know. Sorry, I mean...
I keep calling you that.
It's such a pretty name.
Thank you. I'm glad
my parents picked it for me.
If that's what you want to call me,
I'm fine with you using "Origami."
You can just call me Shido, too.
O-Once I know you better.
Good grief, this is unbearable.
So? What are our plans today?
Good question...
"1. Head to the movie theater
and watch a love story together.
2. Go shopping somewhere fun with her. 3. Skip the boring stuff and go straight to an adult hotel."
Here we go. Your choices, everyone!
"...story together.
...fun with her.
...adult hotel."
Hmm, seems right to me.
I hate to pass up choice one, but going
somewhere they can't talk is a mistake.
What's more, two is a
safe and versatile choice.
There's not a woman alive
who hates shopping.
Shido, we're ready. Two is--
Hold up a sec.
I wanna test out a choice.
Emotional levels unstable!
Origami Tobiichi is distraught!
Damn right she is!
What are you thinking, Shido?!
Talk your way out of it!
A-All right.
S-Sorry, it's this way.
Oh, so that wasn't it...
I thought Origami would be crazy for that...
What? Are you kidding me?
Anyway, go with two. Take the girl shopping.
Roger.
How is her happiness level now?
Hopefully it didn't drop too much.
About that...
Her emotions are fluctuating, but her
happiness might actually be rising.
Are you serious?
Where are we going shopping?
Um, let's see...
"1. Find her an outfit at a clothing store.
2. Play with animals at the pet shop.
3. Go to a shady pharmacy selling aphrodisiacs and love potions."
Your choices, everyone!
Wait. This has gotta be three.
Huh?!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
You can't take a girl there on a first date!
Origami and aphrodisiacs go together
like peanut butter and jelly, you know?
Origami, this way.
How's this, Origami?
I'm sorry, Itsuka.
I don't really understand
what this store's all about.
O-Oh, really?
Hmm?
Origami, you're...
Huh?
What?! W-Why do I have all this stuff?!
What's the matter with me?
Why did I grab all that?
Don't worry about it. It's my fault for
taking you to that weird store anyway.
I'll buy you an outfit as
an apology. What do you want?
What? No, I can't let you--
It's fine, I got it.
In exchange, let me be the
first to see you wearing it.
That's the only payment I need.
Itsuka, do you make girls cry?
You seem too used to this.
Th-That's not true at all!
Then, I guess I'll take you up on that offer.
And while I'm at it, I should pick out
an outfit you might like.
You make girls cry!
She sees right through you!
Gimme a break.
I never said it's a bad thing.
Shin, Origami went into
a dressing room in the back.
Don't lose sight of her.
Right.
Origami!
What's wrong, Origami?!
I... What am I doing?
Sorry, I'm coming in!
Please don't, Itsuka!
O-Origami?
Did you pick that out because
you thought I'd like it?
No! Don't get me wrong!
I don't even remember taking
these clothes off the rack!
Sorry, yet again...
For some reason, I'm weird today.
Don't let it bother you.
It doesn't even faze me.
Okay, thank you.
Sorry, but I need to use the restroom.
Sure, go ahead.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Origami.
O-Origami?
Th-This isn't what you think!
Your spoon fell off the table,
so I was just picking it up!
Sorry!
This is nothing, don't sweat it.
It'll dry in a jiffy.
O-Origami?!
Huh? Why am I...? No! Believe me, Itsuka!
My body's moving on its own!
Please, believe me!
Origami Tobiichi's emotional
levels have stabilized.
Her happiness meter still remains high.
The mood isn't bad either, so maybe
we can wrap it up in one day.
However, she seems to be
anxious about something.
Perhaps whether Shin will
accept her for who she is or not?
I'm not surprised, after all she did...
All we need is one more push.
Really? So you're done with the AST then?
Yeah, my anemia and mind going
blank are both reasons for it, too.
But I just don't know anymore...
...if wiping out Spirits
is the right thing to do...
I'm sorry. It was a Spirit responsible
for killing your brother, too.
Don't be sorry for it!
Huh?
I'm saying you're not wrong
to think that way to begin with!
I... I mean, my brother would
say the same thing, too!
Itsuka... I'm sorry!
I... I...
Happiness meter climbing!
Maximum value was reached!
Hmm. That must have been
the source of her earlier anxiety.
Shido, it's looking good.
It's about time you dove in for the kill!
Origami!
You all right, Origami?
Yeah...
Thanks.
O-Origami...
Spirit...
Shoot. Her Spirit power is--
Shido! Run away!
O-Origami?
That was...
Inverse type...
...Devil...
What's this I'm sensing?
Shiver. My heart is restless.
Look, that way!
What are you doing?! It's dangerous!
Origami is after me!
The only chance to seal her is while
her Spirit armor is incomplete!
If I run away, the city will get demolished!
I won't let Origami...
...do something like that ever again!
Step back, Shido.
Yggdrafolium?!
We'll use Fraxinus' main battery to break
her Spirit barrier for three seconds.
Use that chance to get close and seal--
Kotori, run!
Kotori!
Why...? Again...?
Origami!
Tohka!
You all right, Shido?
We're here, too!
You guys!
Shido, who in the world is that?
I sense dreadful Spirit power.
That's... Origami.
The transfer student?!
It's too dangerous to fight her.
I should probably tell
you to run away, but...
Will you help me try to save her?!
Isn't it obvious?
Shido is the one who saved me.
Shido made my world possible.
This time, it's my turn to help you!
Thank you, everyone.
Wait for me, Origami!
Where am I?
Did I lose consciousness again?
I thought I was just with Itsuka...
You're...
...me?
What's going on?
These are...
...my...
...memories?
"Middle School Entrance Ceremony"
Shido, we'll distract her!
Suggestion. Go while you can!
Keep it up, Kaguya! Yuzuru!
Gabriel!
Rondo!
March!
What the heck, Natsumi?!
You're such a copycat!
I've always wanted to try that once.
Here we go!
At this rate, he can't even get close...
Shido, you've got to reach her!
Zadkiel, Shiryon!
Yoshino?!
Now's your chance!
Save the transfer student!
Thanks, everyone!
Origami!
Open up... your heart!
I'm the one who killed my dad and mom.
That never happened in this world!
Because Itsuka's brother...
No, because Itsuka himself saved them.
And what about my memories?
Can I ever take back
the truth that I killed them?
That's...
I am you. You are me.
Even if the world is remade,
these memories will always remain.
There's no hope for me now.
So that means you, too...
Stop... Enough, stop!
I... I can't...
Someone...
Someone!
Someone help me!
Origami!
Origami, can you hear me?!
Itsuka?
What? Why is Shido...?
Don't carry the burden alone!
I told you five years ago!
You're not alone! I'm here for you!
All of your sadness and hate--
I'll carry all of it for you!
If you're lost, lean on me!
When something happens
and it's too much, rely on me!
Everything... It's okay
to dump everything on me!
So... So...
Don't let despair take over you!
No matter how many worlds you try to break,
I'll come and do something!
I'll come and save you, no matter
how much despair you're in!
Shido...
I...
Reach out to me, Origami!
I need you, too!
Origami!
I...
Thank you, Shido.
If you weren't here for me,
I would've done something else
I couldn't take back...
The fact that I killed my dad
and mom will never go away...
Nor will my sin of all those
I killed in the original world...
It'll stay with me forever.
Even if it's made to never happen at all.
Origami...
You're right. That's a burden
you'll always have to bear.
Shido, I have to apologize to you, too.
The feelings I've had towards you
were not love or anything like that.
I was just relying on you.
When I lost my parents, I had
no choice... but to cling to you.
I'm honored.
It's because you relied on me
that I was able to free you like this.
Shido...
Oh, yeah, I've got something
of yours to give back.
I held onto more than
just tears for you, right?
Origami...
Shido, I...
Good grief. We're never
gonna learn our limits.
Good morning, Shido.
Morning, Origami.
Shido, I have something
to wipe your tears with.
Thanks.
Wh-What are you doing, Origami?!
School swimsuit.
Retains moisture well.
I got these for you, too.
When all that happened, didn't you say
you never loved me and stuff?
Yeah, which is why...
...my true love begins now.
You better stay away from Shido, Origami!
"Episode Twelve:
'Make Shido Itsuka Swoon'"